RG 005:035, Office of the Governor: Thomas J. Meskill (1971-1975)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Subject File, 1971-1975
  - Residence, Use of (Box A-664)
  - Residency, State (Box A-664)
  - Resignation (Box A-664)
  - Resolution (Box A-664)
  - Resources Management Program (Box A-664)
  - Resources Priority Board (Box A-664)
  - Responsive Government Act (Box A-664)
  - Retired Persons (Box A-664)
  - Retirement, 12 folders (Box A-664)
  - Retirement:, 4 folders (Box A-665)
    - Audit Report (Box A-665)
    - Auditors Report – Comptroller/Retirement Special Appropriations (Box A-665)
    - System – Study Commission (Box A-665)
  - Revenue Bonds Power Authority – State of N.Y. (Box A-665)
  - Revenue – New Ideas (Box A-665)
  - Revenue Sharing, 4 folders (Box A-665)
  - Revenue Sharing, 4 folders (Box A-666)
  - Revenue Sharing: (Box A-666)
    - Administration’s Special Proposals (Box A-666)
    - Conference (Box A-666)
    - Mills Bill H.R. 11950 (Box A-666)
    - National Governor’s Conference (Box A-666)
    - National Citizens Committee (Box A-666)
    - -1970 (Box A-666)
    - -1971 (Box A-666)
    - (Rural Comm. Development) (Box A-666)
    - Seminar (Box A-666)
    - Seminar – Responses to Invitation (Box A-666)
    - September, 1974 (Box A-666)
    - (“Special”) (Box A-666)
  - Revenue Task Force (State) (Box A-667)
  - Rewards (Box A-667)
  - Roaming Dogs (Box A-667)
  - Rocky Hill (Box A-667)
  - Rotary Club (Box A-667)
  - Rural Development (Box A-667)
  - Salaries (Box A-667)
  - Salary Increases – Elected Officials, 3 folders (Box A-667)
  - Sanitarians (Box A-667)
  - Savings Bonds (Box A-667)
  - Science & Astronautics (Box A-667)
  - Science Policies (Box A-667)
  - Scouting (Box A-667)
  - Seale-Huggins Trial (Box A-667)
  - Secretary of the State, 2 folders (Box A-667)
  - Secretary of the State – Audit Report (Box A-667)
  - Sedimentation & Erosion Conference (Box A-667)
  - Selective Service (Box A-667)
  - Senate Page Appointments (Box A-667)
  - Senate, U.S (Box A-667)
  - Senior Citizens (Box A-667)
  - Senior Citizens Conn. Council (Box A-667)
  - Services & Expenditures (Etherington) Commission, 3 folders (Box A-667)
  - Services & Expenditures (Box A-668)
    - (Etherington) Commission, 4 folders (Box A-668)
  - Sewage Disposal System: Licensing Board (Box A-668)
  - Sheltered Workshops: Christmas Donation (Box A-668)
  - Sheriff (Box A-668)
  - Sister City Program (Box A-668)
  - Snowmobiles, 2 folders (Box A-668)
  - Social Security (Box A-668)
  - Social Services, 1974 November 22 (Box A-668)
  - Soldiers, Sailors and Marines; Fund (Box A-668)
  - Soldiers, Sailors and Marines; Fund Audit (Box A-668)
  - Southbury-Mansfield Xmas Pageant – Thank You Letters, 1972 (Box A-668)
  - Southern Office (Governor’s Office – Stamford ), 4 folders (Box A-668)
  - Southern Office (Box A-669)
  - Southern Office – August Opening (Box A-669)
  - Southington Armory (Box A-669)
  - Spanish Language Brochure (Box A-669)
  - Spanish-Speaking Americans, 4 folders (Box A-669)
  - Spanish-Speaking, Governor’s Council on Opportunities for the- (Box A-669)
  - Spanish-Speaking, Governor’s Council on Opportunities for the – (Draft of Report), 1973 (Box A-669)
  - Spanish-Speaking – News Releases (Box A-669)
  - Spanish-Speaking Populations, Problems Encountered by New England’s (NERC) (Box A-669)
  - Spanish-Speaking Task Force (Box A-669)
  - Special Elections (Box A-669)
  - Special Interest Groups (Box A-669)
  - Speech & Hearing Association (Box A-669)
  - Speech Schedule (Governor’s) (Box A-669)
  - Speeding (Box A-669)
  - Sportsmen’s Alliance (Box A-669)
  - Staff Salaries (Box A-669)
  - Stafford Speedway (Box A-669)
  - Stainless Steel Flatware (Box A-669)
  - Stamford Area YMCA (Box A-669)
  - Stamford Armory (Box A-670)
  - Stamps – Commemorative (Box A-670)
  - Standards and Appeal, Board of- (Box A-670)
  - Stanley Works (Box A-670)
  - State Animal (Box A-670)
  - State Armory (Box A-670)
  - State Attorney (Box A-670)
  - State Department – USA (Box A-670)
  - State Governments, Council of, 3 folders (Box A-670)
  - State Insect (Box A-670)
  - State Library Newsletter (Box A-670)
  - State Properties Task Force (Box A-670)
  - State Seal (Box A-670)
  - State Services (Box A-670)
  - State Song (Pending Files) (Box A-671)
  - State Song: A –D (Box A-671)
  - State Song: E – Parks (Box A-672)
  - State Song Penley – Z (Box A-673)
  - State Sunday (Box A-674)
  - States’ Council for Regionalism (Box A-674)
  - Statistics (Box A-674)
  - Steele (Box A-674)
  - Strike Force (Box A-674)
    - “Beep” (Balanced Economic & Environmental Policy) (Box A-674)
    - Clippings (Box A-674)
    - Connecticut Development Bank (Box A-674)
    - Final Report – File Copy (Box A-674)
    - First National Bank of Boston (Box A-674)
    - For Full Employment – Preliminary Information (Box A-674)
    - General (Box A-674)
    - General Correspondence (Box A-674)
    - International Corporation Headquarters in Connecticut (Maconi) (Box A-674)
    - Invitation Lists (Box A-674)
    - Preliminary Matters and Final Report Distribution (Box A-674)
    - Transportation Cost (Schneller) (Box A-674)
    - Vocational Training (Miller) (Box A-674)
  - Subversive Activities (Box A-674)
  - Summer Job Folder (Box A-674)
  - Summer Youth Program (Box A-674)
  - Summit Conference (Box A-674)
  - Sunday Blue Law (Box A-674)
  - Sunday Blue Law – Ice Storm (Box A-674)
  - Sunday Blue Law – Reg. About Relaxation of Enforcement, 1974 January 3 (Box A-674)
  - Surplus (Box A-675)
  - Surplus Seminar, 1973 September (Box A-675)
  - Sympathy Letters (Box A-675)
  - Tape – WESU (Box A-675)
  - Task Force – Information Management (Box A-675)
  - Teacher Negotiations (Box A-675)
  - Teachers – Advisory Board on State Certification of Teachers (Box A-675)
  - Teachers Certification (Box A-675)
  - Teachers Education – Conn. Conference (Box A-675)
  - Teachers Sample Letters on Legislation – Labor Relations (Box A-675)
  - Television (Box A-675)
  - Television Systems (PUC) – Cable Antenna (Box A-675)
  - T.V. Examining Board (Box A-675)
  - Temporary Help (Box A-675)
  - Tenure – Teachers (Box A-675)
  - Testimonial (Box A-675)
  - Thank Yous (Box A-675)
  - Tours (Box A-675)
  - Town Chairman (Box A-675)
  - Town Clerks (Box A-675)
  - Town Government (Box A-675)
  - Town Hall Office Hours (Box A-675)
  - Toxicology Laboratory (Box A-675)
  - Trailer Parks (Box A-675)
  - Trailers – Development Commission (Box A-675)
  - Transportation (Box A-675)
  - Treasurer, 7 folders (Box A-675)
  - Treasurer, 5 folders (Box A-676)
  - Treasurer – Annual Report, 1972 (Box A-676)
  - Treasurer – “Connecticut Nutmeg Securities” (Box A-676)
  - Treasurer Reports, 3 folders (Box A-676)
  - Treasury Department Newsletter (Box A-676)
  - Tree Exam. Board (Box A-676)
  - Trucking – “National Truck Strike-Out”, 1974 January 15 (Box A-677)
  - Trucks (Box A-677)
  - Unions (Box A-677)
  - United Nations (Box A-677)
  - UN Day (Box A-677)
  - U.S. Savings Bond (Box A-677)
  - U.S. Treasury Dept. (Box A-677)
  - Urban Affairs (Box A-677)
  - “Urban Affairs Report” (Box A-677)
  - Urban League (Box A-677)
  - Vacation – Travel Advisory Council (Box A-677)
  - Veterans, 6 folders (Box A-677)
  - Veterans Administration (Box A-677)
  - Veterans Assistance Letter (Box A-677)
  - Veterans Benefit – Bonus, 2 folders (Box A-677)
  - Veterans Fact Sheet (Box A-678)
  - Veterans Day Reception, 1973 November 12 (Box A-678)
  - Veterans Form Letter List, 4 folders (Box A-678)
  - Veterans Home and Hospital (Box A-678)
  - Veterans Home & Hospital Commission (Box A-678)
  - Veterans Home & Hospital – Rocky Hill Vacancy (Box A-678)
  - Veterans Home/Conn. Valley Hospital (Box A-678)
  - Veterans (Jobs) (Box A-678)
  - Veterans Leg. H.R. 12628 (Box A-678)
  - Veterans – Rocky Hill Veterans Hospital, 2 folders (Box A-678)
  - Veterans/Southeastern Branch Facility (Box A-679)
  - Veterans – Vietnam Veterans (Box A-679)
  - Veto Messages (Box A-679)
  - Veto Messages, 1974 (Box A-679)
  - Veto of House of Good Shepherd Bill – Senate Bill 2006 (Box A-679)
  - Vice President (Box A-679)
  - Vietnam (Box A-679)
  - Vietnam Bonus (Box A-679)
  - Voluntary Action, Governor’s Council on, 4 folders (Box A-679)
  - Volunteerism Material (Box A-679)
  - Voter – Complaint (Box A-680)
  - Voter Registration, 4 folders (Box A-680)
  - Voter Registration – GOP (Box A-680)
  - Voter Support (Box A-680)
  - Voting – Age 18 (Box A-680)
  - Voting Eligibility (Box A-680)
  - Wage and Price Control – Economic Stabilization Program, Phase II (Box A-680)
  - Wage and Price Freeze (Box A-680)
  - Wage and Price, Phase II (Box A-680)
  - Washington Office, 2 folders (Box A-680)
  - Washington Office, 5 folders (Box A-681)
  - Washington Office – Federal Legislation Summaries (Box A-681)
  - Watergate, 2 folders (Box A-681)
  - Waterways (Box A-681)
  - Welfare Report – CPTV (Box A-681)
  - Welfare/Torrington Office (Box A-681)
  - Well Drilling Board (Box A-681)
  - Whales (Box A-681)
  - Weather Control Board (Box A-681)
  - White House, 6 folders (Box A-682)
  - White House – Cabinet Committee on Spanish Speaking (Box A-682)
  - White House Fellows (Box A-682)
  - Willimantic Library Center (Box A-682)
  - Wiretap (Box A-682)
  - Women: Governor’s Commission on the Status of Women (Box A-682)
  - Women: League of Women Voters, “Legislative Newsletter” (Box A-682)
  - Xerox (Box A-682)
  - Year End Reports (Box A-682)
  - Young American Medals for Bravery (Box A-682)
  - Young Republican Executive Board (Box A-682)
  - Youth Development Program (Including Summer) (Box A-682)
  - Youth Leadership (Box A-682)
  - Zoning (Box A-682)
  - Zoos (Box A-682)
  - Zullo (Box A-682)
- Series 3. Pending File, 1974-1975
  Correspondence and memoranda awaiting decision or completion of action.
  Alphabetical by correspondent, with a few folders by agency at the end.
  - Records (Box A-683)
- Series 4. Memoranda, 1972-1975
  Originals and copies of memoranda written by, for or to Gov. Meskill on many subjects.
  Roughly chronological.
  - Records (Box A-684)
- Series 5. Public Interest Correspondence, 1971-1975
  These are retained examples of a much larger volume (see Disposal Inventory 29) of letters from the public expressing opinions about various issues.
  - Abortion (Box A-685)
  - Drug abuse (Box A-685)
  - Farm workers (Box A-685)
  - Blue laws (Box A-686)
  - Budget (Box A-686)
  - Bus strike (Box A-686)
  - Public Utility rate hike (Box A-686)
  - Bus strike (Box A-687)
  - Children’s letters (Box A-687)
  - Daylight saving time (Box A-687)
  - Energy (Box A-687)
  - Fuel adjustment (Box A-687)
  - Gas rationing (Box A-687)
  - Gas rationing (Box A-688)
  - Merritt Parkway (Box A-688)
  - Interstate 84 (Box A-689)
  - Pornography (Box A-689)
  - State police pay raise (Box A-689)
  - Taxation (Box A-690)
- Series 6. Yellows, 1970-1975
  Yellow carbon copies of outgoing letters written by the Governor and his staff.
  Alphabetical by addressee in the following groups.
  - 1970 A – Z (Box A-691)
  - 1971 D – I (A – C missing) (Box A-691)
  - 1971 J – S (Box A-692)
  - 1971 T – Z (Box A-693)
  - A – B (Box A-694)
  - B (Box A-695)
  - C (Box A-696)
  - C – D (Box A-697)
  - E – G (Box A-698)
  - G – H (Box A-699)
  - H – K (Box A-700)
  - K – L (Box A-701)
  - M (Box A-702)
  - M – O (Box A-703)
  - P – R (Box A-704)
  - R – S (Box A-705)
  - S – T (Box A-706)
  - U – Z (Box A-707)
- Series 7. Agency Files, 1971-1975
  - Agriculture Department (Box A-708)
    - Correspondence (Box A-708)
    - Dairy Division (Box A-709)
    - Publications (Box A-709)
    - Tree Protection Agency (Box A-709)
    - Resources / Inter-departmental messages (Box A-709)
    - Gordon Allen’s Legislative File (Box A-709)
    - Miscellaneous Information (Box A-709)
  - Annual Reports (Box A-709)
    - 1971 (Box A-709)
      - Accountancy – Health (Box A-709)
      - Higher Education – Workmen’s Compensation (Box A-710)
    - 1972 (Box A-710)
      - Accountancy – Mental Retardation (Box A-710)
      - Military – Workmen’s Compensation (Box A-711)
    - 1973 (Box A-711)
      - Accountancy – Plumbing and Piping Examiners (Box A-711)
      - Podiatry – Tax (Box A-712)
    - 1974 (Box A-712)
      - Accountancy – Transportation (Box A-712)
      - Treasury – Women, Status of (Box A-713)
  - Attorney General (Box A-713)
  - Bond Commission (Box A-714)
  - Bond Commission (Box A-715)
  - Bond Commission (Box A-716)
  - Commerce Department (Box A-717)
    - Subject Files (Box A-718)
      - Audit Report, 3 folders (Box A-718)
      - Bradley Gateway Status (Box A-718)
      - Chamber of Commerce (Box A-718)
      - Committee of Concern, 3 folders (Box A-718)
      - Committee of Concern for Jobs (Box A-718)
      - Letters to Company Executives (Box A-718)
      - Conn. Development Authority, 2 folders (Box A-718)
      - Commerce Container-port (Box A-718)
      - Commerce “Dear Friend” Letter (Box A-718)
      - Expo (Box A-718)
      - Fact Sheet (Box A-718)
      - Fortune 500 (Box A-718)
      - Conn. Industrial Building (Box A-718)
      - Commission (Box A-718)
      - Industrial Development Bonds (Box A-718)
      - Ingraham Industries (Box A-718)
      - Okay Industries (Box A-718)
      - Letters (Box A-718)
      - Mag Card, 2 folders (Box A-718)
      - Minority Enterprises (Box A-718)
      - Monthly Reports (Box A-718)
      - Research Commission (Box A-718)
      - Speaking Engagements (Box A-718)
      - Switzerland Trip, 2 folders (Box A-718)
      - Telefunken (Box A-718)
      - Telegram (Box A-718)
    - Oil Refinery Task Force Files (Box A-719)
  - Community Affairs Department (Box A-720)
    - Commissioner & Deputy Commissioners, 4 folders (Box A-720)
    - Subject Files: (Box A-720)
      - Action (Box A-720)
      - Action, Conn. (Box A-720)
      - Action – Grant Vista Volunteers (Box A-720)
        - New London – Groton Volunteers, Inc. (Box A-720)
      - Action/Vista – NH Volunteers (Box A-720)
      - Action/Vista – Waterbury NOW (Box A-720)
      - Advisory Council (Box A-720)
      - Advisory Council on Community Affairs (Box A-720)
      - ADC – Aid to Dependent Children (Box A-720)
      - A-95 Process (Box A-720)
      - Anti-Poverty Agencies (Box A-720)
      - Audit (Box A-720)
      - Audit Report (Box A-720)
      - Better Communities Act (Box A-720)
      - B.A.R. Black Active Republicans (Box A-720)
      - Book for Children (Conn.) (Box A-720)
      - Bond Commission (Box A-720)
        - February (Box A-720)
        - February Bond for DCA (Box A-720)
        - March, 1972 (Box A-720)
        - March Bond Agenda (Box A-720)
        - 1972 April 28 (Box A-720)
        - April Bond Commission (Box A-721)
        - January Bond Commission (Box A-721)
        - May Bond Commission (Box A-721)
        - June Bond (Box A-721)
        - Bond Agenda; 1972 May (Box A-721)
        - Bond Commission; 1971 November (Box A-721)
        - Bond Commission; 1971 December (Box A-721)
      - Bond Commission; 1972 January (Box A-721)
      - July Bond Agenda – July 23 (Box A-721)
      - Bond Commission Meeting – 1971 August (Box A-721)
      - September Bond (Box A-721)
      - October Bond; 1971 October 22 (Box A-721)
      - Budget (Box A-721)
      - Budget Explanation, 1971 (Box A-721)
      - Budget, 1972 (Box A-721)
      - Budget’s View (Box A-721)
      - Cable Television (Box A-721)
      - CAP (Box A-721)
      - Booklet/Capitol Improvements Programming (Box A-721)
      - Carabetta Housing (Box A-721)
      - Cities (Box A-721)
      - Clemente, Roberto Memorial Fund (Box A-721)
      - Community Action Program (Box A-721)
      - Connecticut Humanities Council (Box A-721)
      - CPAP (Comprehensive Planning Assistance Program) (Box A-721)
      - CPAP (Box A-721)
      - Consultants (Box A-721)
      - Dauntless Lane Apartments (Box A-722)
      - Day Care (Box A-722)
      - Day Care Funding (Box A-722)
      - Day Care Building Code & Fire Code (Box A-722)
      - Day Care Mag Card Letters (Box A-722)
      - Day Care Nutrition Symposium – Mag Cards (Box A-722)
      - Day Care Fee, Standard Child – Mag Card (Box A-722)
      - Day Care Guidelines (Box A-722)
      - Day Care Programs (Box A-722)
      - CDC Letters (Pickens) (Box A-722)
      - Day Care Mag Card Letters (Box A-722)
      - Day Care Proposal & Berdon’s Housing Proposal, Governor’s Conference (Box A-722)
      - Day Care Guideline, 1971 November 1 (Box A-722)
      - Day Care – State’s Role (Box A-722)
      - Day Care Task Force (Box A-722)
      - Day Care Good Shepherd (Box A-722)
      - Day Care – Danbury (Box A-722)
      - Day Care – Greenwich (Box A-722)
      - Day Care – Groton- Miner (Box A-723)
      - Day Care – Mt. Olive (Box A-723)
      - Day Care – Naugatuck (Box A-723)
      - Day Care – New London, 1-177-CDC (Box A-723)
      - Day Care – New London, 1-180-CDC (Box A-723)
      - Day Care – Willimantic (Box A-723)
      - Day Care – Petitions (Box A-723)
      - Day Care – Woman’s League Day Care Centers (Box A-723)
      - Directory (Box A-723)
      - Disaster Assistance (701) (Box A-723)
      - Drug Programs (Box A-723)
      - Educational Instruction (Box A-723)
      - Emergency Loan (Box A-723)
      - Energy (Box A-723)
      - Energy, Solar (Box A-723)
      - Energy Letter (Box A-723)
      - Environmental Impact (Box A-723)
      - Evaluation Team (Housing), 1971 (Box A-723)
      - Farmers Home Administration (Box A-723)
      - Federal Assistance for Community Development Activities Legislation (Box A-723)
      - Federal Legislation (Box A-723)
      - Governor’s Day Trips (Box A-723)
      - Head Start, 1 folder plus envelope (postcards) (Box A-723)
      - HEW – Health, Education & Welfare (Box A-723)
      - Health Programs (Box A-723)
      - Heating Fuel Funds (Box A-723)
      - Heating, Solar (Box A-723)
      - Hill Cooperative Youth Service (Box A-723)
      - History, Community Affairs, 2 folders (Box A-723)
      - Housing, 2 folders (Box A-724)
      - Housing Fact Sheet (Box A-724)
      - Housing Authority (Box A-724)
      - Housing Code (Box A-724)
      - Housing Elderly, 2 folders (Box A-724)
      - Housing Inquiries (Box A-724)
      - Housing Program, Section 23 Leased (Box A-724)
      - Housing Legislation, Low Rent (Box A-724)
      - Housing – Mobile Home Ad Hoc Committee (Box A-724)
      - Housing Moderate Rental Program (Box A-724)
      - Housing Pilot (Box A-724)
      - Housing Rehabilitation (Box A-724)
      - Housing Mobile Homes (Box A-724)
      - Housing Tax Abatement (Box A-724)
      - Housing Study (Box A-724)
      - Housing Leasing Center/Acuedo (Box A-724)
      - Housing, Title I of & Community Development Act (Box A-724)
      - Housing National Homes Corp. (Box A-724)
      - Housing – New Britain (Box A-724)
      - Housing Site Development (Box A-725)
        - HSD: Danbury – Beaver St. Interfaith Social Action Corporation (Box A-725)
        - Hartford HSD – North Arsenal (Box A-725)
        - Hartford HSD – Project Rehab (Box A-725)
        - New London HSD – Manwaring Reed-Coit (Box A-725)
        - Application for Execution Grant – Strawberry Hill Avenue Site (Box A-725)
        - Stamford HSD – Clinton Avenue & Strawberry Hill (Box A-725)
        - HSD: Waterbury – Saarsfield Terrace (Box A-725)
        - HSD: Waterbury –Better Housing Assn. (Box A-725)
      - HRD Letters (Pickens) (Box A-725)
      - Institute for the Future (IFF) (Box A-725)
      - Human Resources Development Job Corps (Box A-725)
      - Job Vacancy (Box A-725)
      - Labor/Personnel: Institute of Public Service (UCONN) (Box A-725)
      - Legislation (Box A-725)
      - Equal Opportunity Activities (Box A-725)
      - Legislation, 1972 (Box A-725)
      - Letter to Atty. General Killian re: to PA 73-607 (Box A-725)
      - Bureau of Local Assistance (Box A-725)
      - Bureau of Local Governments (Box A-725)
      - Migrant Farm Workers, 2 folders (Box A-725)
      - Minority Business (Box A-725)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box A-725)
      - Model Cities (Box A-725)
      - National Economic Development (Box A-725)
      - National Headstart Schedule (Box A-725)
      - Neighborhood Youth Corps (NYC) (Box A-726)
      - New England Farmers’ Work Council (Box A-726)
      - New England Non-Profit Housing Development Corp. (Box A-726)
      - OEO – Office of Economic Opportunity (Box A-726)
      - OEO – FAC (Federal Aid Coord.) FIX (Fed. – Inf. Exchange System) (Box A-726)
      - OEO Legislation (Box A-726)
      - OIC (Box A-726)
      - OMB Circular A-70 (Box A-726)
      - Personnel (Box A-726)
      - Pickens, Memos to (Box A-726)
      - Poverty (Box A-726)
      - Press Releases, 2 folders (Box A-726)
      - Progress Reports (Box A-726)
      - Public Works & Economic Development Act of 1965 (Box A-726)
      - Publications (Box A-726)
      - Puerto Rican Legal Services (Box A-726)
      - Releases (Box A-726)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box A-726)
      - Self-Help Programs (Box A-726)
      - Sparkman’s Bill (Box A-726)
      - Spanish American (Box A-726)
      - Spanish Institute (Box A-726)
      - Speaking Engagements (Box A-726)
      - Status Report of Applications (Box A-726)
      - Status Reports (Box A-726)
      - Summer Programs, 1969-1970 (Box A-726)
      - Summer, ABCD, 1971 (Box A-726)
      - Summer Programs, 1971 (Box A-726)
      - Summer Program, 1972 (Box A-727)
      - Tax Abatements, 9 folders (Box A-727)
        - Folder: 1. Bridgeport – 1st Baptist (Box A-727)
        - Folder: 2. Hartford – Garden Street (Box A-727)
        - Folder: 3. No. Haven – Antillean Manor (Box A-727)
        - Folder: 4. No. Haven – St. Luke’s (Box A-727)
        - Folder: 5. No. Haven – Student Housing York Street (Box A-727)
        - Folder: 6. Stamford – Coleman Towers (Box A-727)
        - Folder: 7. Waterbury – Lambda Rho Apartments (Box A-727)
        - Folder: 8. Waterbury – Prospect Towers (Box A-727)
        - Folder: 9. Waterbury – Savings Towers (Box A-727)
      - TWLAP (Tolland-Windham Legal Asst. Program) (Box A-727)
        - Court (Box A-727)
        - OEO Grant CG-1001-B/1 (2 folders) (Box A-727)
        - Correspondence & Petitions to ans. (Box A-727)
        - Tolland-Windham Legal Asst. Prog., Inc. vs. Thomas J. Meskill, et al (Box A-727)
        - Grants T & TA (Training & Tech. Asst.) (Box A-727)
      - Uniform Relocation Assistance Act – P.A. 838 of 1971 (Box A-727)
      - Van Block Housing (Box A-727)
      - Vehicular Noise Abatement Program (Box A-727)
      - Veterans Grant (Box A-727)
      - WACAP – Total Package (Box A-727)
      - Youth (Box A-727)
      - Youth Bridge (Box A-727)
      - Zoning (Box A-727)
    - Town Files (Box A-728)
      - Ansonia (Box A-728)
      - Ballouville (Box A-728)
      - Baltic (Box A-728)
      - Bethany (Box A-728)
      - Branford (Box A-728)
      - Bridgeport (ABCD (Box A-728)
      - Bridgeport (Box A-728)
      - Bridgeport – C.O.O.L. (Box A-728)
      - ABCD Summer Employment (Box A-728)
      - Bridgeport: (Box A-728)
        - (ABCD) Grants (Box A-728)
        - Beardsley & Pequonnock Apartments (Box A-728)
        - Day Care, Headstart, etc. (Box A-728)
        - Housing (Box A-728)
        - Housing NERC Contract (Box A-728)
        - Modular Housing (Box A-728)
        - Housing “Rehab City” HUD (Box A-728)
        - Housing Rotary Housing Corp. (Box A-728)
        - Housing Waterview Housing Site (Box A-728)
        - Housing I.B.D. (Project OWN) (Box A-728)
      - Bristol (Box A-728)
      - Canaan & No. Canaan Housing (Box A-728)
      - Cheshire (Box A-728)
      - Clinton (Box A-728)
      - Colchester (Box A-728)
      - Coventry (Box A-728)
      - Danbury (Box A-728)
      - Danbury – CAC – Grants (Box A-728)
      - Danbury – SSR (Box A-728)
      - Derby (Box A-728)